Guide to the City Planning Commission, Pittsburgh, Pa. Records, 1928-1962 AIS.1976.17
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Oversize Material, VII.
  - Groundwork & Inventory for Pittsburgh Plan, Central Business District, Change in Assessed Valuation of Land from 1931 to 1940, Map, 1944
  - Groundwork & Inventory for Pittsburgh Plan, Central Business District, Principal Existing Land Uses, Map, 1944
  - Groundwork & Inventory for Pittsburgh Plan, Relationship of Existing Major Street Plan to Residential, Business and Industrial Improvement Districts, Map, 1944
  - Groundwork & Inventory for Pittsburgh Plan, Relationship of Existing Street Car and Bus Routes to Residential, Business and Industrial Improvement Districts, Map, 1944
  - Tentative Study for Pittsburgh Plan, Pittsburgh Portion of a New Regional Highway Network in Relation to Natural Pattern of Improvement Districts, Map, 1944
  - Tentative Study for Pittsburgh Plan, Pittsburgh Portion of a New Regional Highway Network, Where Coinciding and Where Not Coinciding with Thorofares of Existing Major Street Plan, Map, 1944
  - Tentative Study for Pittsburgh Plan, Pittsburgh Portion of a New Regional Highway Network, Where Coinciding and Where Not Coinciding with Fixed Car Trackage of Existing Mass Transportation Routes, Map, 1944
  - Tentative Study for Pittsburgh Plan, Principal Existing Pools of Employment in Relation to Pittsburgh Portion of a New Regional Highway Network, Map, 1944
  - Tentative Study for Pittsburgh Plan, Central Business District, Scheme of Off-Street Automobile Parking Terminals in Relation to Collector-Distributor Traffic Loop, Map, 1944
  - Tentative Study for Pittsburgh Plan, Central Business District, One of Several Studies of Street Car Circulation, Map, 1944
  - Key Map to Identify Improvement Districts as Shown by Master Plan Document no. 1, Generalized Plan of Propspectives Land Uses, Approved by the Planning Commission, November 1947 (Map-case 7-7, Folder 8)
  - Land Value, Average City Assessed Valuation per Square Foot of Land, by Blocks, Map, June 1937 (Map-case 7-7, Folder 9)
  - Distribution of 1602 Dwelling Structures Demolished in Pittsburgh from January 1, 1934 to December 31, 1936, as recorded by Bureau of Building Inspection, Map, March 1937
  - Street Map, City of Pittsburgh, July, 1940
  - Industrial Employment, Location, Classification and Number of Employees of Industries Employing 100 or More Persons, City of Pittsburgh, Map, 1937
  - Graphic Map of Average Rent, 1940, Dwelling Units, by Blocks (Combined Where Alike) Within Residential Improvement Districts, June 1944
  - Transportation, Location of Street Car and Local Bus Lines, Railroad and Long Distance Bus Terminals, Inclines, City of Pittsburgh, Map, 1937
  - Community Facilities, City of Pittsburgh, Map, August 1937
  - Road map of Allegheny County, 1952
  - Athletic Field Service Areas and Total Population, City of Pittsburgh, Map, April 1942 (Map-case 7-7, Folder 10)
  - Swimming Pool Service Areas and Total Population, City of Pittsburgh, Map, April 1942
  - Junior-Senior Service Areas and Child Population, City of Pittsbugrh, Map, April 1942
  - Junior-Senior Service Areas, City of Pittsburgh, Map, 1942
  - Square Feet of Playground Area to Child Population, 1940, by Service Areas, City of Pittsburgh, All Facilities Included in Master Recreation Plan, Sheet 1 of 2, Map, June 1942
  - Square Feet of Playground Area to Child Population, 1940, by Service Areas, City of Pittsburgh, All Facilities Included in Master Recreation Plan, Sheet 2 of 2, Map
  - Square Feet of Playground Area to Child Population, 1940, by Service Areas, City of Pittsburgh, All Facilities Included in Master Recreation Plan Plus Others Operated by B. R. and All Elementary School Play Areas, Sheet 1 of 2, Map, June 1942
  - Square Feet of Playground Area to Child Population, 1940, by Service Areas, City of Pittsburgh, All Facilities Included in Master Recreation Plan Plus Others Operated by B. R. and All Elementary School Play Areas, Sheet 2 of 2, Map
  - Summer Recreation Facilities in Relation to Service Areas, Map, June 1942
  - Summer Recreation Facilities in Relation to Service Areas, Indicating Those Operated During 1941, Map, June 1942
  - Senior Playground Areas, Related to Study Areas and Pittsburgh Census Tracts, Map, September 1940
  - Junior and Senior Playground Areas, Adjusted to Study Areas and Pittsburgh Census Tracts, Map, September 1940
  - Athletic Field Areas, Related to Study Areas and Pittsburgh Census Tracts, Map, September 1940
  - Athletic Field Areas, Adjusted to Study Areas and Pittsburgh Census Tracts, Map, September 1940
  - Swimming Pool Areas, Related to Study Areas and Pittsburgh Census Tracts, Map, September 1940
  - Swimming Pool Areas, Adjusted to Study Areas and Pittsburgh Census Tracts, Map, September 1940
  - Swimming Pool Areas, Adjusted to Study Areas and Pittsburgh Census Tracts, Indicating Pools Now Used by B. P. E. and New Pools Proposed, Map, September 1940
  - Proposed Recreation Service Areas, City of Pittsburgh, Map, July 1942 (Map-case 7-7, Folder 11)
  - Recreation Facilities of the City and Board of Public Education, Pittsbugrh, Map, April 1942
  - Summer Recreation Facilities and Junior-Senior Service Areas, 1943, Master Recreation Plan, City of Pittsburgh, Map, January 1942
  - Recreation Facilities, City of Pittsburgh Dept. of Parks and Recreation, Map, 1960
  - Analysis of Recreation Facilities, City of Pittsburgh, Chart, June 1942
  - Resident Deaths Caused by Tuberculosis in Junior-Senior Service Areas During 1930-1939, Map, June 1942; 108.
  - Resident Deaths Caused by Infection Diseases in Junior-Senior Service Areas During 1930-1939, Map, 1942
  - Tubercular Death Rate, Resident Deaths to Total Population in Junior-Senior Service Areas During 1930-1939, Map, August 1942
  - Infection Disease Death Rate, Resident Deaths to Total Population in Junior-Senior Service Areas During 1930-1939, Map, August 1942
  - Individuals Charged with Delinquency at Juvenile Court in Junior-Senior Service Areas During 1930-1939, Map, June 1942
  - Juvenile Delinquency Case Rate, Deliquency Cases to Child Population in Junior-Senior Service Areas During 1930-1939, Map, August 1942
  - 28th Ward Sketches, 1969 (Map-case 7-7, Folder ?)
  - Sewer and Street Paving Sheets, 1910-1927 (Map-case 7-7, Folder ?)
  - Corliss Street Tunnel Drainage, 1942 (Map-case 7-7, Folder ?)
  - Rosegarden Road Sewer Reconstruction, 1975 (Map-case 7-7, Folder ?)
- Parks and Recreation Facility Plans, 1917-1991; VIII.
  - Abel-Long Playground, 1977 (Map-case 32-8, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Contains 5 sheets of design.
  - Banksville Swimming Pool, 1964-1975 (Map-case 32-8, Folder 2)
    Contains 6 sheets of drawings and plans including: pool site plan, notes, sewer reconstruction on Banksville Road, and ballfield construction.
  - Beechview Playground, 1944-1960 (Map-case 32-8, Folder 3)
  - Chartiers Playground, 1917-1963 (Map-case 32-8, Folder 4)
    Contains 9 sheets of sewer and playground plans.
  - Dunbar Ballfield, 1978 (Map-case 32-8, Folder 5)
    Contains 3 sheets of ballfield design.
  - East Carnegie Playground, 1986 (Map-case 32-8, Folder 6)
    Contains 4 sheets of design.
  - Hershell Park, 1953-1979 (Map-case 32-9, Folder 1)
    Contains 20 pages of service building design plans, park design, and park improvement.
  - McArdle Road Planting Project, 1971 (Map-case 32-9, Folder 2)
    Contains 2 sheets of planting design.
  - Oakwood Ballfield, 1973-1978 (Map-case 32-9, Folder 3)
    Contains 4 pages of ballfield design and playground equipment.
  - Olympia Park, 1923-1954 (Map-case 32-9, Folder 4)
    Contains 23 pages of repair plans, park design, and pool design.
  - Pauline Avenue Playground, 1957 (Map-case 32-10, Folder 1)
    Contains 6 sheets of playground design.
  - Pittsburgh Race Maps, 1991 (Map-case 32-10, Folder 2)
    Contains 3 sheets of the route of the marathon, liberty bridge police presence, and the route of the bicycle race.
  - Shaler Playground, 1948 (Map-case 32-10, Folder 3)
    Contains 1 sheet of improvement to playground.
  - Sheraden Park, 1939-1973 (Map-case 32-10, Folder 4)
    Contains 47 sheets of sewer plans for ballfield, swimming pool design, ballfield design, drawings, and field house designs.
  - Stratmore Playground, 1973 (Map-case 32-10, Folder 5)
    Contains 1 sheet of playground design.
  - Townsend Playground, 1966 (Map-case 32-10, Folder 6)
    Contains 4 sheets of playground design.
  - Tropical Park, 1961 (Map-case 32-10, Folder 7)
    Contains 6 sheets of park design.
  - West End Park, 1937-1964 (Map-case 32-10, Folder 8)
    Contains 10 pages of sketched plans, shelter plans, and rehabilitation plans.
  - Westwood Playground, 1973 (Map-case 32-10, Folder 9)
    Contains 2 sheets of lighting design and additions to playground.